{
    "subject": "resource/Ferrari",
    "predicate": "property/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Maranello",
    "human_readable": "Ferrari is located in Maranello.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9645499587059021,
            "question": "Is Ferrari based in Maranello?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7122529745101929,
            "question": "Where is Ferrari located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6064016222953796,
            "question": "In which country is Ferrari situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3826422691345215,
            "question": "Is Maranello known for its automotive industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33576616644859314,
            "question": "What city is associated with Ferrari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2892451882362366,
            "question": "What is the location of Ferrari's main factory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2843571901321411,
            "question": "What is the geographical origin of Ferrari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24717067182064056,
            "question": "In which Italian city can you find Ferrari's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1961721032857895,
            "question": "Where are most Ferrari cars manufactured?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14688977599143982,
            "question": "To which Italian city is the Ferrari brand linked?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferrari is located in Maranello.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3190_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are most Ferrari cars manufactured?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3190_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which Italian city can you find Ferrari's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3190_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geographical origin of Ferrari?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3190_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3190_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text explicitly states that \"Ferrari's headquarters is located in Maranello, Italy.\" (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3190/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt) and also mentions the \"Maranello Factory\" as being located in Maranello, Italy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Ferrari\u2019s headquarters and factory are located in Maranello, Italy. Therefore, the statement \"Ferrari is located in Maranello\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}